{
    "subject": "resource/Steve_Warnstadt",
    "predicate": "ontology/region",
    "object": "resource/Iowa",
    "human_readable": "Steve Warnstadt is from Iowa.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9871625304222107,
            "question": "Is Steve Warnstadt originally from Iowa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9597883820533752,
            "question": "Is Iowa where Steve Warnstadt currently resides?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9089402556419373,
            "question": "Where is Steve Warnstadt from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7771942019462585,
            "question": "What state is Steve Warnstadt associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7181419730186462,
            "question": "Where did Steve Warnstadt grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7038928866386414,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Steve Warnstadt's origins?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7034358978271484,
            "question": "Steve Warnstadt's birthplace is in which state?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6539217829704285,
            "question": "What can you tell me about Steve Warnstadt's place of origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5572409629821777,
            "question": "What is Steve Warnstadt's home state?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20278914272785187,
            "question": "Iowa is the home state of whom?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Steve Warnstadt is from Iowa.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1075_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Steve Warnstadt's home state?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1075_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you tell me about Steve Warnstadt's place of origin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1075_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Steve Warnstadt's birthplace is in which state?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1075_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1075_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1075_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1075_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1075_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1075_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1075_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1075_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1075_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1075_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1075_68.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Steve Warnstadt is from Iowa\" based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because all four documents mention that Steve Warnstadt was born in Sioux City, Iowa (August 2, 1967), and he served as an Iowa State Senator."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Steve Warnstadt's political career, which includes serving as the Iowa State Senator. This supports the statement that Steve Warnstadt is from Iowa."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}